shopmissa.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy I Shop Miss A

Home /  Privacy Policy I Shop Miss A

ShopMissA.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly.   
This notice describes our privacy policy. We are committed to the protection of your personal information in accordance with applicable privacy laws, including GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation).

This policy (the “Policy”) sets out how we collect, use, manage, transfer, disclose, and store personal information in the course of doing business. You agree that this Policy applies to you as an individual and is separate from, and does not amend or modify, any contractual arrangements between you or your organization and us, nor create any rights in you under any such contract.  The examples contained in this Policy are illustrations only and are not intended to be exhaustive.

**What Personal Information About Customers Does ShopMissA.com Gather?  
** The information we learn from our customers helps us personalize and continually improve your MissAStores.com experience. Here are the types of information we gather.

    * **Information You Give Us:  **We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way.  
You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such proposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
    * **How we collect information:  **We collect personal information in a number of ways, including:

    * (a) where you provide information directly to us, including through our website or when you participate in promotions or competitions run by us;

(b) where you interact directly with our employees and such other persons acting for us or on our behalf, such as our customer service team, including from electronic queries sent to us via email;

(c) where you provide information directly to us during a recruitment process;

(d) from third parties, such as our service providers;

(e) through referrals from individuals or other entities;

(f) through marketing and business development events;

(g) where you provide feedback to us;

(h) from related entities in our corporate group; and

(i) from publicly available sources of information.

If you do not wish for your personal information to be collected in a way anticipated by this Policy, we will accommodate your request. If we do comply with your request, or you choose to not provide your personal information to us, or you provide us with inaccurate or incorrect information, we may not have sufficient information to conduct our business and we may be limited:

(a) in our ability to properly conduct our operations, including providing products and services to you;

(b) in our ability to keep you informed about your orders or our business;

(c) in considering your application for employment with us; and

(d) in our ability to respond to an inquiry or request.

    * **Automatic Information:  **We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use “cookies”, and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses ShopMissA.com.
    * **E-mail Communications** : To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from ShopMissA.com if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Customer Profile Preferences.  
Information you submit to us via our contact form is transferred outside the EEA and stored on our third party email and customer service systems. Our  _email provider_  is Klaviyo Inc. You can access their privacy policy here: [www.klaviyo.com/privacy](http://www.klaviyo.com/privacy). Our customer service system provider is Zendesk. You can access their privacy policy here: <https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/eu-data-protection/>  _Country of storage_ : United States. This country is not subject to an adequacy decision by the European Commission.  _Safeguard(s) used_ : our third party email provider has self-certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield

**What About Cookies?**

Cookies are unique identifiers that we transfer to your device to enable our systems to recognize your device and to provide such features such as Recommended for You, and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. The Help feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on’s settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of ShopMissA.com essentials features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any ShopMissA.com products and services that require you to Sign In.

**Does MissAStores.com Share the Information It Receives?  
** Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We do not sell your personal information to third parties for any reason. We share customer information only as described below.

    * **Third-Party Service Providers:  **We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
    * **Protection of ShopMissA.com and Others:  **We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of ShopMissA.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
    * Server information: Information collected when you visit our website is transferred outside of the EEA and stored on the servers of our third party hosting company , Shopify. You can access their privacy policy here: [www.shopify.com/privacy](http://www.shopify.com/privacy)  _Country of storage_ : Canada and the United States.  _Safeguard(s) used_ : our third party hosting provider has self-certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield.

  * **With Your Consent:  **Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
  * We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finishes using a shared computer.

**Are Children Allowed to Use ShopMissA.com?**

ShopMissA.com.com does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children’s products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use ShopMissA.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. Children under 13 years of age should not send any information about themselves to ShopMissA.com.

**Conditions of Use, Notices and Revisions**

If you choose to visit ShopMissA.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Texas. If you have any concern about privacy and ShopMissA.com please contact us with a thorough description and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and out Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers

**Questions and complaints**

ShopMissA.com is the data controller in respect of your personal information under this Policy. If you have a question about how we handle personal information, or wish to submit a complaint about our management of personal information (including if you believe that we have managed your personal information in breach of applicable privacy laws), you may contact our Privacy Officer:

Attention: Privacy Officer  
ShopMissA.com  
2025 Royal Lane Suite 370. Dallas TX 75229  
Email: cs@shopmissa.com
